var quizQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the keyword used to create an object in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["var", "object", "class", "new"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of loop in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["for", "while", "repeat", "do-while"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a way to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["var", "let", "const", "declare"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      "function myFunction() {}",
      "function = myFunction() {}",
      "myFunction() {}",
      "var myFunction = function() {}",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the use of 'this' keyword in javascript",
    answers: [
      "It refers to the object that the function is a method of",
      "refers to the object that the function is a property of",
      "refers to the object that the function is a class of",
      "refers to the object that the function is a constructor of",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How to add an element at the end of an array in javascript?",
    answers: [
      "arr[arr.length] = element;",
      "arr.append(element);",
      "arr.push(element);",
      "arr.add(element);",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of data in javascript?",
    answers: ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "Function"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "What is the use of typeof operator in javascript?",
    answers: [
      "it returns the type of the variable",
      "it returns the value of the variable",
      "it returns the length of the variable",
      "it returns the position of the variable",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How to delete an element of an array by its value in javascript?",
    answers: [
      "delete array[value];",
      "array.remove(value);",
      "array.splice(array.indexOf(value), 1);",
      "array.pop(value);",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the use of JSON.parse() in javascript?",
    answers: [
      "It converts a JSON string into a JavaScript object",
      "It converts a JavaScript object into a JSON string",
      "It converts a string into a number",
      "It converts a number into a string",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
];
